<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hello, it&#39;s Eliza speaking</title>
    <link>http://elizaspeaking.com/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hello, it&#39;s Eliza speaking</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Eliza Garton</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 23:08:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://elizaspeaking.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The start.</title>
      <link>http://elizaspeaking.com/post/the-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 23:08:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://elizaspeaking.com/post/the-start/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello world, it&amp;rsquo;s Eliza speaking. Today I&amp;rsquo;m starting at the start. It is the 1st of the month, my
first week of university for the year, and this is my first ever blog post! If you&amp;rsquo;ve found yourself
here reading, thank you so much for taking the time! I hope that my blog brings you great joy, relief,
support, life hacks, craft tips, a simple smile; I just hope that you can take something positive away
with you. I believe that one single smile or fleeting feeling of happiness can change the course of your
day. We all have ups and downs through life, so I&amp;rsquo;ll share some of mine with you on my blog, starting
with how I chose its name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent a lot of time with the thought in the back of my mind of what to call my blog. I brainstormed
all kinds of &amp;lsquo;clever ways&amp;rsquo; (some of them were really terrible) to use my name or something about me in
the name but nothing really stuck. I settled on this name because ever since I was allowed to answer the
telephone at home, I always answered it with &amp;ldquo;Hello, it&amp;rsquo;s Eliza speaking.&amp;rdquo; If you know me personally,
you&amp;rsquo;ll know that I still answer the phone this way! I figured it&amp;rsquo;s never going to go away and I am
obviously the author of this blog, so what the heck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you follow me on Instagram (and you should 😉), you will know that I posted there about starting
this blog. Well, that was one month ago today! I set my self a deadline to get my first post
published and I made it! (Just). This also coincides with my first week of uni for the year.
It was great to reconnect with the new friends that I made last year and we&amp;rsquo;re off to a cracking
start with some exceptional lecturers and tutors. I&amp;rsquo;ve got good vibes about this year so let&amp;rsquo;s hope
2017 comes up with the goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/Xi8epx7.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look Mum, I made a thing! It&amp;rsquo;s a thing that I wanted to get finished before uni started but, after
cutting everything out and ironing on the interfacing, I sat down at my sewing machine and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t
stitching properly! All the settings were fine but the stitching was all bunchy. I almost had a
breakdown right there at my machine because I had anticipated sitting down to finish it for weeks only
to have my machine break! My breakdown was averted by awesome hugs from my guy. Nonetheless, today I
sat at my sewing machine and did a bit of light maintenance which got it going again and I was able
to finished it this afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/dyiCoR7.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a pouchy kind of pencil case and it&amp;rsquo;s perfectly sized to fit my bullet journal in and a bunch
of stationary (stationary addict over here). Oh yeah, a bullet journal is something new for me that
I started this year. Have you heard of this diary/planner/journal craze? I cottoned onto it only
last year, but no I can&amp;rsquo;t remember where I first saw it. Anyway, I did heaps of reading into what it
is, how you do it, if it would be beneficial for me etc etc and now that I&amp;rsquo;ve started, yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m
in love!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/WdfpGMA.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll post about that another time but for now, thanks so much for stopping by! My blog is still in
renovation mode so I hope you don&amp;rsquo;t mind putting up with that for a little while until I totally
work it out and make it look pretty. Peace and love ✌️️&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>